http://www.customshop.com/shop/privacy-policy

Stores
Toledo, OH (Corporate)
/
The Custom Shop Clothiers - Custom Dress Shirts | Privacy Policy
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the bottom of each page in our site. The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on The Custom Shop Clothier’s website. On some pages, you can make online purchases. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.) The Way We Use Information We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We may also use the email address to send newsletters and/or promotional materials. You may un-subscribe at any time by replying to any email sent by The Custom Shop at sales@customshop.com.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by calling our national headquarters toll-free at (888) 744-7806. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. How To Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (888) 744-7806 or send us an email at sales@customshop.com.
Collar Styles
Cuff Styles
Measuring Guide
FAQ
Privacy Policy
About Us
5 Ways to Order
Site Map
